[
    {
      "question": "What do we call the period of 4 Sundays before Christmas?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Advent",
        "b": "Epiphany",
        "c": "Christmas Period"
      },
      "correctAnswer": "Advent"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Christmas tree in Trafalgar Square has been donated by which country since 1947?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Denmark",
          "b": "Sweden",
          "c": "Norway"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Norway"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the first brand to use Santa Claus in its advertisements?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Pepsi",
          "b": "Coca-Cola",
          "c": "McDonald"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Coca-Cola"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which popular Christmas song was originally composed for Thanksgiving?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Silent Night",
          "b": "Run Rudolph Run",
          "c": "Jingle Bells"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Jingle Bells"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote the novel “A Christmas Carol”?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Charles Dickens",
          "b": "Oscar Wilde",
          "c": "William Shakespeare"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the highest grossing movie about Christmas of all time?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Love Actually",
          "b": "Home Alone",
          "c": "The Polar Express"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Home Alone"
      },
      {
        "question": "The tradition of putting up and decorating a Christmas tree began in which country?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "France",
          "b": "Italy",
          "c": "Germany"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Germany"
      },
      {
        "question": "When does the Boxing Day take place annually?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "On December 23rd",
          "b": "On December 26th",
          "c": "On December 27th"
        },
        "correctAnswer": ". On December 26th"
      },  {
        "question": "What is the original meaning of Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "To commemorate the death of Jesus Christ",
          "b": "To remember the birth of Jesus Christ",
          "c": "To honour Christianity"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "To remember the birth of Jesus Christ"
      },
      {
        "question": "The first Christmas card was sent in which year?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "1802",
          "b": "1843",
          "c": "1895"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "1843"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is not another name for Santa Claus?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Red Uncle",
          "b": "Kris Kringle",
          "c": "Saint Nick"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Red Uncle"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which country does a witch rather than Santa Claus drops gifts through the chimney for kids on Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Finland",
          "b": "Poland",
          "c": "Italy"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Italy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which are the two typical colours of Christmas candy canes?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Green and red",
          "b": "Red and blue",
          "c": " White and red"
        },
        "correctAnswer": " White and red"
      },
      {
        "question": "Including Rudolph, how many reindeers pull the sleigh and help Santa Claus send gifts to kids on Christmas Eve?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "7",
          "b": "8",
          "c": "9"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the most popular decorative ornament placed on top of a Christmas tree?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Angels",
          "b": "Christian crosses",
          "c": "Stars"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Angels"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was Jesus Christ born?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Jerusalem",
          "b": "Bethlehem",
          "c": "Tel Aviv"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Bethlehem"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which wild bird is usually featured on Christmas cards in Britain?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Black-capped chickadee",
          "b": "Cardinal",
          "c": "Robin"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Robin"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which play was written by William Shakespeare as a Christmas present?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "The Merry Wives of Windsor",
          "b": "Two Gentlemen of Verona",
          "c": "Winter’s Tale"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "The Merry Wives of Windsor"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is traditionally hidden in a Christmas pudding?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "star",
          "b": "A silver coin",
          "c": "A small piece of paper"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "A silver coin"
      },
      {
        "question": "The “true love” of the singer gives him how many gold rings in “The 12 Days of Christmas”?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "1",
          "b": "3",
          "c": "5"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": " What is the name for the traditional dish at Christmas dinner that wraps sausages in bacon?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Pigs in bacon",
          "b": "Pigs in layers",
          "c": "Pigs in blankets"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Pigs in blankets"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first person to introduce the Christmas tree to the United Kingdom?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "A royal member",
          "b": "A merchant",
          "c": "A priest"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "A royal member"
      },
      {
        "question": "How to say “Merry Christmas” in Spanish?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Felices fiestas",
          "b": "Feliz Nuevo",
          "c": "Feliz Navidad"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Feliz Navidad"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to superstition, in which direction should you always stir when making mince pies on Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Clockwise",
          "b": "Anticlockwise",
          "c": "It depends"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Clockwise"
      },
      {
        "question": "The traditional “Father Christmas” or Santa Claus in Britain was originally not dressed in red. Which colour did he wear?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Blue",
          "b": "Golden",
          "c": "Green"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Green"
      },
      {
        "question": "There are two islands named Christmas in the world. One is located in the Indian Ocean and the other is located in which ocean?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Pacific Ocean",
          "b": "Atlantic Ocean",
          "c": "Arctic Ocean"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Pacific Ocean"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the first use of Christmas candy canes?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "To use as a dessert at Christmas dinner",
          "b": "To keep noisy kids quiet during the church service",
          "c": "To use as a dessert at Christmas dinner"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "To keep noisy kids quiet during the church service"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which famous Christmas song was played on the trenches of both German and English on Christmas Eve 1914?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Silent Night",
          "b": "O Holy Night",
          "c": "O Little Town of Bethlehem"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Silent Night"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many points does a snowflake traditionally have?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "5",
          "b": "6",
          "c": "7"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "6"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the colour of the berries on Mistletoe?",
        "answers": {
          "a": " White",
          "b": "Red",
          "c": "Green"
        },
        "correctAnswer": " White"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who wrote A Christmas Carol?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Charles Dickens",
          "b": "Washington Irvin",
          "c": "Douglas Jerrold"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Santa’s wife?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Jessica Mary Clause",
          "b": "Mary Clause",
          "c": "Jess Mary Clause"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Jessica Mary Clause"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the star of the Christmas movie Jingle All the Way?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Arnold Schwarzenegger",
          "b": "Randy Kornfield",
          "c": "David Adkins"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the star of the movie titled White Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Bing Crosby",
          "b": "Danny Kaye",
          "c": "Rosemary Clooney"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Bing Crosby"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Christmas food is it considered good luck to eat one of on each of the 12 days of Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Mince Pies",
          "b": "Turkey",
          "c": "Chicken"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Mince Pies"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you leave for Santa?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Milk and cookies",
          "b": "Candy Canes",
          "c": "Nut Cracker "
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Milk and cookies,"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the world’s largest nativity scene?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Einsiedeln,",
          "b": "Helsinki",
          "c": " Norway"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Einsiedeln,"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do Christians associate with the wreath?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "The crown of thorns worn by Jesus",
          "b": "Red candles",
          "c": "Purple candles"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "The crown of thorns worn by Jesus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What’s the most popular Christmas play featuring toys that come to life?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "The Nutcracker",
          "b": "elf",
          "c": "rudolph"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "The Nutcracker"
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the Holy Bible, Jesus Christ was born in a",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Stable",
          "b": "shed",
          "c": "Kennels"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Stable"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who helps Santa Claus in making his gifts?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Elves and Mrs. Claus!,",
          "b": "Rudolph",
          "c": "Reindeer"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "Elves and Mrs. Claus!,"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who once stole Christmas?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "The Grinch",
          "b": "Elf",
          "c": "Reindeer"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "The Grinch"
      }
      
  ]